

# CONTACT ME

C

210-454-1039



davidtunnell9@gmail.com



San Antonio, TX / Remote



davidtunnell.com/



linkedin.com/in/david-tunnell

#### **SKILLS SUMMARY**

Full Stack Web Development, HTML/CSS, JavaScript, jQuery, Responsive Design, Bootstrap, Burma CSS, OOP, React.js, **Relational Databases (SQL** Server, MySQL), NoSQL Databases (MongoDB), Node.js / Express.js, 3rd Party API Consumption, API Creation / Consumption, JSON, AJAX, WordPress, PHP, Laravel, C#, .NET Core / 5.0, ASP.NET MVC, ASP.NET Web Forms, WEB API, XML/XAML, SSMS, Selenium, Gherkin, XPath, Manual Testing, Automated Testing, Agile / Scrum, JIRA, Confluence, Requirements Gathering, System Integrations, UX Process

#### **CERTIFICATIONS**

Certified Tactical Agilist Tactical Agile

ServiceNow Certified System Administrator ServiceNow

SAFe SPC Scaled Agile

# **David Tunnell**

# Software Developer

Seasoned IT professional with 8 years of experience working in various capacities on software projects looking to move back into a software development role. Enjoys being challenged and engaged with projects that require me to work outside my comfort zone and knowledge set, especially while collaborating with a team.

#### WORK EXPERIENCE

# **IT Applications Project Manager**

LMI • San Antonio, TX / Remote • July 2020 - April 2021

Managed a team of 13 people to deliver complex software solutions and system integrations utilizing critical platforms that the organization relies on every day to complete work.

#### **Scrum Master**

LMI • San Antonio, TX / Remote • Oct 2018 – July 2020

Implemented the entire Scrum/Agile process for the ServiceNow software team. Worked with a large variety of corporate groups to develop complex software requirements.

#### **Software Development Engineer in Test**

LMI • San Antonio, TX / Remote • April 2018 – Sept 2019

Developed Unit Tests, Page Object Models (XPath), and Gherkin based automation using a proprietary .NET based automation testing framework build using Selenium.

#### **Software Development Consultant**

Contractor • Remote • Nov 2015 - April 2018

Developed software for a variety of projects from a prescription medication database to a startups web app using C#/.NET as well as PHP/Laravel.

#### **Software Developer**

Zachry Group • San Antonio, TX • May 2013 - Nov 2015

Developed ASP.NET/C# corporate web applications and maintained WordPress/PHP based websites.

More details and history on Linkedin.

#### **EDUCATION**

# University of North Carolina at Chapel Hill

Full Stack Development Bootcamp - 2021

## The University of Texas at Austin

Master of Business Administration - 2013

### University of Maryland - University College

Bachelor of Computer Science - Cum Laude - 2013

# University of Phoenix

Bachelor of Science, Business – 2010